<resources>
    <string name="app_name">MAD Tasks</string>
    <string name="UI"><b>UI Overview</b>\n
        All user interface elements in an Android app are built using View and ViewGroup objects. A View is
        an object that draws something on the screen that the user can interact with. A ViewGroup
        is an object that holds other View (and ViewGroup) objects in order to define the layout
        of the interface.

Android provides a collection of both View and ViewGroup subclasses that offer you common input
        controls (such as buttons and text fields) and various layout models (such as a linear
        or relative layout).
      \n\n

  <b>User Interface Layout</b>\n
        The user interface for each component of your app is defined using a hierarchy of View and
        ViewGroup objects, as shown in figure 1. Each view group is an invisible container
        that organizes child views, while the child views may be input controls or other
        widgets that draw some part of the UI. This hierarchy tree can be as simple or
        complex as you need it to be (but simplicity is best for performance).
    </string>
    <string name="UI2">
        To declare your layout, you can instantiate View objects in code and start building a tree,
        but the easiest and most effective way to define your layout is with an XML file. XML offers
        a human-readable structure for the layout, similar to HTML.
    </string>
    <string name="notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="signin">SignIn</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>


    <string name="displyHint">Enter a value</string>

    <string name="btnOneText">1</string>
    <string name="btnTwoText">2</string>
    <string name="btnThreeText">3</string>
    <string name="btnFourText">4</string>
    <string name="btnFiveText">5</string>
    <string name="btnSixText">6</string>
    <string name="btnSevenText">7</string>
    <string name="btnEightText">8</string>
    <string name="btnNineText">9</string>
    <string name="btnZeroText">0</string>

    <string name="btnClearText">CLEAR</string>
    <string name="btnParenthesesOpenText">(</string>
    <string name="btnParenthesesCloseText">)</string>
    <string name="btnDivideText">รท</string>
    <string name="btnMultiplyText">ร</string>
    <string name="btnAddText">+</string>
    <string name="btnSubtractText">-</string>
    <string name="btnDecimalText">.</string>
    <string name="btnEqualsText">=</string>

    <string name="btnBackspace"> </string>
    <string name="signout">Signout</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="form">Form</string>
    <string name="ui">UI</string>
    <string name="calculator">Calculator</string>
</resources>